SAM THOROGOOD: Hey, everyone.
SAM THOROGOOD：大家好。
It's Sam here.
是山姆。
CHRIS JOEL: And I'm Chris.
克里斯·乔尔：我是克里斯。
SAM THOROGOOD: So Chris is from the Polymer team.
SAM THOROGOOD：因此Chris来自Polymer团队。
And on today's Santa Tracker, Developer Diary,
在今天的圣诞老人追踪器，开发人员日记中，
we're going to talk a little bit about how Santa Tracker uses
我们将讨论圣诞老人追踪器的使用方式
Polymer to be more productive.
聚合物可以提高生产率。
So what's Polymer?
那么什么是聚合物？
CHRIS JOEL: So Polymer is a library
CHRIS JOEL：So Polymer是一个图书馆
that helps you take advantage of some of the latest browser
可以帮助您利用一些最新的浏览器
features, such as web components.
功能，例如Web组件。
SAM THOROGOOD: Cool.
SAM THOROGOOD：很酷。
And so we've been using Santa for quite a few years now.
因此，我们使用圣诞老人已经有很多年了。
We use it in a bunch of different ways.
我们以多种不同方式使用它。
So in a broad sense, the whole site is basically
因此，从广义上讲，整个站点基本上是
in one custom element, one Polymer element
在一个自定义元素中，一个聚合物元素
called Santa App.
称为圣诞老人应用程序。
But actually, that then contains things
但是实际上，那包含了东西
like Santa Chrome, which is really
就像圣诞老人的Chrome，
our UI around the edge of the page.
我们位于页面边缘的用户界面。
You see the kind of toolbar and things like that.
您会看到工具栏的种类以及类似的内容。
We've also got some elements that you never actually see.
我们还提供了一些您从未真正看到的元素。
So the Santa Tracker router handles the changes in the URL
因此，Santa Tracker路由器可以处理URL中的更改
up here.
上面这儿。
So whenever we click on a scene, like this boatload scene,
因此，每当我们单击一个场景（例如此船载场景）时，
this router is actually listening to the URL
该路由器实际上正在监听URL
and then bonding that route back to the Santa App
然后将该路由绑定回圣诞老人应用程序
so it can change the scene being loaded.
因此它可以更改正在加载的场景。
CHRIS JOEL: That's really cool.
克里斯·乔尔：真的很酷。
So you made those custom elements.
因此，您做了那些自定义元素。
SAM THOROGOOD: Yeah, and even though there's
SAM THOROGOOD：是的，即使有
no visual representation, I think it's really interesting.
没有视觉表现，我认为这真的很有趣。
And then we actually lazyload that scene,
然后我们实际上是延迟加载该场景，
which is really cool.
这真的很酷。
CHRIS JOEL: Very cool.
克里斯·乔尔：太酷了。
SAM THOROGOOD: So when we're loading and running Polymer,
SAM THOROGOOD：因此，当我们加载并运行Polymer时，
how do we test it?
我们如何测试呢？
How do we see how fast it loads?
我们如何看它加载的速度？
CHRIS JOEL: Well, I always like to use the built-in profiler
CHRIS JOEL：嗯，我一直喜欢使用内置的探查器
in Chrome dev tools.
在Chrome开发者工具中。
SAM THOROGOOD: Cool.
SAM THOROGOOD：很酷。
CHRIS JOEL: So in order to do that, usually what I do first
克里斯·乔尔：因此，为了做到这一点，通常我首先要做的是
is I go to the application tab and I clear all my site data.
我转到应用程序选项卡，然后清除所有站点数据。
SAM THOROGOOD: Great.
SAM THOROGOOD：很好。
That's good, because we have a lot of caching
很好，因为我们有很多缓存
and a lot of offline ready stuff.
还有很多离线准备的东西。
So we want to clear all those resources
所以我们想清除所有这些资源
so it feels like you're loading it for the first time.
因此感觉就像您是第一次加载它。
CHRIS JOEL: Yep.
克里斯·乔尔：是的。
And then you go over to your performance tab,
然后转到“效果”标签，
and you click this button--
然后单击此按钮-
start profiling and reload page.
开始分析并重新加载页面。
SAM THOROGOOD: Sounds good.
SAM THOROGOOD：听起来不错。
CHRIS JOEL: So the profile takes a few seconds.
克里斯·乔尔（CHRIS JOEL）：因此，个人资料需要几秒钟。
And then when it's done, you get a lot of nice things.
然后，完成后，您会得到很多不错的东西。
So at the top here, I actually have
所以在这里顶部，我实际上有
a timeline that shows the painting of the page
显示页面绘画的时间线
as it's loading in.
正在加载。
Underneath that, I can see all of my network resources.
在此之下，我可以看到所有网络资源。
So I can get a sense of when they
这样我就可以了解他们何时
finish loading in relative to all the JavaScript that's
完成相对于所有JavaScript的加载
executing.
执行。
SAM THOROGOOD: And we're scrolling the mouse wheel here
SAM THOROGOOD：我们在这里滚动鼠标滚轮
to zoom in and out, to deep dive or not.
放大和缩小，是否进行深潜。
CHRIS JOEL: One of the things I've
克里斯·乔尔：我做过的一件事
added that's a little special is I've used the standard user
补充一点，就是我使用了标准用户
timing API, and I've instrumented all of the custom
计时API，我已经检测了所有自定义
elements on the app.
应用程序上的元素。
So here you can see the Santa App element was created.
因此，在这里您可以看到圣诞老人应用程序元素已创建。
And it took about 250 milliseconds.
而且大约花费了250毫秒。
SAM THOROGOOD: That's the whole site, I guess.
SAM THOROGOOD：我想是整个网站。
CHRIS JOEL: Right.
克里斯·乔尔：对。
That's the entire site's execution lifecycle.
这就是整个站点的执行生命周期。
And then underneath that, I can see things like, oh, iron icon.
然后在此之下，我可以看到类似铁图标的东西。
SAM THOROGOOD: Why does the icon take 26 milliseconds to load?
SAM THOROGOOD：为什么图标需要26毫秒的加载时间？
CHRIS JOEL: I don't know, but that's probably
克里斯·乔尔（CHRIS JOEL）：我不知道，但这可能是
something we should look into.
我们应该研究的东西。
SAM THOROGOOD: Yeah, interesting.
SAM THOROGOOD：是的，很有意思。
CHRIS JOEL: You can see all of the children elements
CHRIS JOEL：您可以看到所有的子元素
inside of Santa App are represented here
圣诞老人应用程序的内部在这里表示
in this Flame chart.
在此火焰图表中。
So I can get a sense of which ones are most expensive.
因此，我可以了解哪些是最昂贵的。
SAM THOROGOOD: So you would see this normally anyway,
SAM THOROGOOD：因此，无论如何您通常都会看到这种情况，
but if you look in the description below,
但是如果您查看下面的说明，
you'll see some resources that Chris
您会看到克里斯的一些资源
has written to help you actually just label
已写信帮助您实际上只是在贴上标签
the elements properly.
适当的元素。
Normally, you'd just see the functions themselves
通常，您只会看到函数本身
and not know which element it's actually being called on.
而且不知道它实际上是在调用哪个元素。
So that's really great.
这真是太好了。
So this year, one thing we're going to do
所以今年，我们要做的一件事
is actually upgrade Polymer.
实际上是升级聚合物。
So we're on, I think, version 1.7 right now.
我想我们现在就在1.7版上。
We used to be on 0.5 back in the day,
我们以前是0.5
and now we're upgrading to 1.10.
现在我们升级到1.10。
And the goal of 1.10 is then to flip to 2.0.
然后，1.10的目标是过渡到2.0。
There's a lot of versions floating around.
有很多版本可供选择。
What does this mean?
这是什么意思？
Why are we doing this?
我们为什么要这样做呢？
CHRIS JOEL: Yeah, so the upgrade from 1.10 to 2.0 is going
CHRIS JOEL：是的，所以从1.10升级到2.0
to get you in a place where you can start building custom
使您处于一个可以开始定制的地方
elements using standard ES6 classes.
使用标准ES6类的元素。
The Polymer, as any open source project, is evolving over time.
与任何开源项目一样，Polymer也在不断发展。
And now we're trying to put our users in a place
现在我们试图将我们的用户放在一个地方
where they can easily start taking advantage
他们可以轻松地开始利用的地方
of some of the latest JavaScript features in the web platform.
Web平台中的一些最新JavaScript功能。
SAM THOROGOOD: Right.
SAM THOROGOOD：好的。
So previously, you wrote a Polymer function
所以之前，您编写了Polymer函数
and gave it an object.
并给了它一个对象
And actually, now, you write a regular class name
实际上，现在，您编写一个常规的类名
that you inherit from a Polymer element, right?
是从Polymer元素继承的，对不对？
CHRIS JOEL: Yep.
克里斯·乔尔：是的。
SAM THOROGOOD: Yeah, which is much more idiomatic these days.
SAM THOROGOOD：是的，这几天越来越惯用了。
CHRIS JOEL: And it's very important to migrate up to 2.0,
CHRIS JOEL：迁移到2.0版本非常重要，
because it puts you on the trajectory
因为它使您走上了轨道
to later versions of Polymer.
到更高版本的Polymer。
We have Polymer 3.0 in preview now.
我们现在有预览版的Polymer 3.0。
And that's going to enable you to use things like JavaScript
这将使您能够使用JavaScript之类的东西
modules and also get onto the NPM package manager
模块并进入NPM软件包管理器
for distributing your--
用于分发您的-
SAM THOROGOOD: And by the time you're
SAM THOROGOOD：等到您
watching this we may already be there.
看着这个，我们可能已经在那了。
So check it out and have a look at Polymer
所以检查一下，看看聚合物
and see how we're using it in Santa Tracker.
并查看我们如何在Santa Tracker中使用它。
So that's pretty much all we have to talk about today.
这就是我们今天要谈论的几乎所有内容。
Thanks for watching.
感谢收看。
Remember, you can always go check out
请记住，您可以随时退房
the source code for Santa Tracker and have a look at it
圣诞老人追踪器的源代码，看看它
yourself and build this on your own time.
自己建立自己的时间。
And yeah, thank you, Chris, for being here as a guest star.
是的，谢谢克里斯，因为我是来宾之星。
CHRIS JOEL: Yep.
克里斯·乔尔：是的。
Yay.
好极了。
SAM THOROGOOD: See you.
SAM THOROGOOD：见。
You can subscribe to the Google Chrome Developer channel
您可以订阅Google Chrome开发者频道
down here or check out some other great videos along here.
在这里或在此处查看其他一些很棒的视频。